<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>C422</title>
    <link>/authors/yangjin/</link>
    <description>Recent content on C422</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>C422 &amp;copy; {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/authors/yangjin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Keynote] CPU analysis and Software design summary</title>
      <link>/post/keynote-20190530-yangjin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/keynote-20190530-yangjin/</guid>
      <description>The CPU of hardware analysis and the summary of software design experience in previous time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Award] National third award on 2018 China Collegiate Computing Contest (Top 10%)</title>
      <link>/accomplishment/yangjin-awd-fccompete2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/accomplishment/yangjin-awd-fccompete2018/</guid>
      <description>China University Student Service Outsourcing Innovation and Entrepreneurship Competition is a national competition jointly organized by the Ministry of Commerce of China, the Ministry of Education of China and the Wuxi People&amp;rsquo;s Government</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Project] Campus intelligent auditing system based on Deep Learning and WeChat Applet</title>
      <link>/accomplishment/yangjin-pro-nationalutp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/accomplishment/yangjin-pro-nationalutp/</guid>
      <description>2018 Tianjin School level National Undergraduate Training Programs for Innovation and Entrepreneurship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/authors/yangjin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/authors/yangjin/</guid>
      <description>Now I am studying software engineering at Tianjin Normal University. I have a strong interest in computer programming languages ​​and machine learning models, and like to brainstorm and organize my own knowledge system.
Competition experience: As a project member, I participated in the tenth section of China University Student Service Outsourcing Innovation and Entrepreneurship Competition. As the project leader, I established Tianjin Normal University School-level Daiso Project.
Research direction: The main research direction at present is machine learning and computer networks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>