<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>C422</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on C422</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>C422 &amp;copy; {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	    <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Keynote] The knowledge points of Python and Machine Learning</title>
      <link>/post/keynote-20190606-lisen/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/keynote-20190606-lisen/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-sharing-session-mainly-includes-the-knowledge-points-of-python-and-machine-learning&#34;&gt;The sharing session mainly includes the knowledge points of  &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Python&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Machine Learning&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;1-python&#34;&gt;1. Python&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;code&gt;@ Decoration&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;code&gt;__call__&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;2-the-algoriyhm-of-machine-learning&#34;&gt;2. The algoriyhm of Machine Learning&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SVM（Support Vector Machine）&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KNN（k-NearestNeighbor）&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Click &lt;a href=&#34;https://cdn.coden.hk/c422/weekly-keynote/2019-06-06-lisen/keynote.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Download PDF&lt;/a&gt; and see details！&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Keynote] CPU analysis and Software design summary</title>
      <link>/post/keynote-20190530-yangjin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/keynote-20190530-yangjin/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Click &lt;a href=&#34;https://cdn.coden.hk/c422/weekly-keynote/2019-5-31-yangjin/5.30工作室分享会.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;PDF&lt;/a&gt; and see details.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;point-out-an-error&#34;&gt;Point out an error&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the question that &lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;Why is Thread instead of Process in ‘4 Core 8 Thread&amp;rsquo; ?”&lt;/strong&gt; in PDF&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Firstly，a point should be clearly，which is that &lt;strong&gt;Thread in &amp;lsquo;4 Core 8 Thread&amp;rsquo; is different with Thread in operating system&lt;/strong&gt;.The former refers to the &lt;strong&gt;physical unit&lt;/strong&gt; in the CPU, the latter refers to the &lt;strong&gt;logical unit&lt;/strong&gt; in the operating system, so the problem does not hold!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Keynote] Research share</title>
      <link>/post/keynote-20190525-jiaojinlong/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/keynote-20190525-jiaojinlong/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Weekly keynote, topic: &lt;strong&gt;Research share&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;ppt&#34;&gt;PPT&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The topic I shared is Research share.Please refer to the attachment for details： &lt;a href=&#34;https://cdn.coden.hk/c422/weekly-keynote/2019-05-25-jiaojinlong/%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A0%E5%88%86%E4%BA%AB.pptx&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Download&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Keynote] Paper writing and CI</title>
      <link>/post/keynote-20190516-wangpenghao/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/keynote-20190516-wangpenghao/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Weekly keynote, topic: &lt;strong&gt;Paper writing and CI&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;ppt&#34;&gt;PPT&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The topic I shared is Paper writing and Continuous Integration.Please refer to the attachment for details： &lt;a href=&#34;https://coden-cdn.sfo2.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/c422/weekly-keynote/2019-05-16-wangpenghao/学习小结0516-王鹏浩.pptx&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Download&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Publication] Design and Implementation of Credit Evaluation System for Healthy Aged Service</title>
      <link>/accomplishment/lisen-pub-pension/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/accomplishment/lisen-pub-pension/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;abstract&#34;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We introduce Collie，an online platform to assess the quality of nursing home service powered by machine learning, which enables user to choose a serial of selected algorithms for different demand. Previous research has proposed the point on how to measure the quality of nursing home service. But traditional service relies on manual investigation which present serval problems like the process of rating quality is complex and insufficient. For the above problems, Collie focus on supporting users to assess the quality of nursing home service. Within the service assessment, we develop a serial of algorithms to deal with different dataset. But more importantly, different database has different features, a group of algorithms is not enough to fulfill users demand. Therefore, we propose a system which enables users choose highly competitive algorithms to solve their problem. To support the core idea, we provide a high performance infrastructure features asynchronous I/O, fast and error tolerant data pipeline. Through a series of experiments, we show that our system outperforms the baseline significantly in terms of system performance, algorithm accuracy. Promising result has been retrieved from our algorithm which indices MAE of 0.5 at sample dataset.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Project]  Hierachical Attention for Speech Emotion Recognition</title>
      <link>/accomplishment/jiaojinlong-pro-nationalutp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/accomplishment/jiaojinlong-pro-nationalutp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Introduction: Using hierarchical attention mechanisms at the level of sentences and words to improve the accuracy of speech emotion recognition. This project is supported by National Natural Science Foundation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Keynote] Programming Language</title>
      <link>/post/keynote-20190509-zhaoyiqin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/keynote-20190509-zhaoyiqin/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Weekly keynote, topic: &lt;strong&gt;programming language&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;whiteboard-notes&#34;&gt;Whiteboard Notes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://coden-cdn.sfo2.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/c422/weekly-keynote/2019-05-09-zhaoyiqin/1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://coden-cdn.sfo2.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/c422/weekly-keynote/2019-05-09-zhaoyiqin/2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Project] Research on Supporting Theory and Innovation Model of Cross-border Service for Healthy Elders</title>
      <link>/accomplishment/lisen-pro-pension/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/accomplishment/lisen-pro-pension/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In view of the problems existing in the credit information of China&amp;rsquo;s old-age care industry, in order to establish a sound old-age service credit information system and guarantee the quality of old-age service, the standard of pension service credit standard and the trust mechanism and reputation algorithm based on old-age service are formulated for development. The Health Support + “Integrated Support Platform provides theoretical support for credit assessment and provides a comprehensive solution for the credit problems in the aged care service. The project is supported by the National Key Basic Research Development Program (973 Program).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Scholarship] Wang Kechang Culture and Technology Innovation Scholarship (&lt;1%)</title>
      <link>/accomplishment/zhaoyiqin-sch-wangkc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/accomplishment/zhaoyiqin-sch-wangkc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TODO: Add details&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Publication] Deep Spectrum Feature Representations for Speech Emotion Recognition</title>
      <link>/accomplishment/zhaoyiqin-pub-deepsp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/accomplishment/zhaoyiqin-pub-deepsp/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dl.acm.org/citation.cfm?doid=3267935.3267948&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Download&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;abstract&#34;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Automatically detecting emotional state in human speech, which plays an effective role in areas of human machine interactions, has been a difficult task for machine learning algorithms. Previous work for emotion recognition have mostly focused on the extraction of carefully hand-crafted and tailored features. Recently, spectrogram representations of emotion speech have achieved competitive per- formance for automatic speech emotion recognition. In this work we propose a method to tackle the problem of deep features, herein denoted as deep spectrum features, extraction from the spectrogram by leveraging Attention-based Bidirectional Long Short-Term Mem- ory Recurrent Neural Networks with fully convolutional networks. The learned deep spectrum features are then fed into a deep neural network (DNN) to predict the final emotion. The proposed model is then evaluated on the Interactive Emotional Dyadic Motion Cap- ture (IEMOCAP) dataset to validate its effectiveness. Promising results indicate that our deep spectrum representations extracted from the proposed model perform the best, 65.2% for weighted accuracy and 68.0% for unweighted accuracy when compared to other existing methods. We then compare the performance of our deep spectrum features with two standard acoustic feature repre- sentations for speech-based emotion recognition. When combined with a support vector classifier, the performance of the deep feature representations extracted are comparable with the conventional features. Moreover, we also investigate the impact of different fre- quency resolutions of the input spectrogram on the performance of the system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;cite&#34;&gt;Cite&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;@inproceedings{Zhao:2018:DSF:3267935.3267948,
 author = {Zhao, Ziping and Zhao, Yiqin and Bao, Zhongtian and Wang, Haishuai and Zhang, Zixing and Li, Chao},
 title = {Deep Spectrum Feature Representations for Speech Emotion Recognition},
 booktitle = {Proceedings of the Joint Workshop of the 4th Workshop on Affective Social Multimedia Computing and First Multi-Modal Affective Computing of Large-Scale Multimedia Data},
 series = {ASMMC-MMAC&#39;18},
 year = {2018},
 isbn = {978-1-4503-5985-6},
 location = {Seoul, Republic of Korea},
 pages = {27--33},
 numpages = {7},
 url = {http://doi.acm.org/10.1145/3267935.3267948},
 doi = {10.1145/3267935.3267948},
 acmid = {3267948},
 publisher = {ACM},
 address = {New York, NY, USA},
 keywords = {attention mechanism, bidirectional long short-term memory, fully convolutional networks, spectrogram representation, speech emotion recognition},
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Award] CADC 2018 China Aeromodelling Design Challenge · The First Prize</title>
      <link>/accomplishment/lisen-awd-cadc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/accomplishment/lisen-awd-cadc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This contest is held at Nanjing,China , Inc to all students over the great China area.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Award] National third award on 2018 China Collegiate Computing Contest (Top 10%)</title>
      <link>/accomplishment/yangjin-awd-fccompete2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/accomplishment/yangjin-awd-fccompete2018/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Based on Natural Language Processing and WeChat Applet, this project designs a set of convenient proof of study and campus activity review system, which makes the process of issuing student certificates and campus activities approval standardized, institutionalized, procedural and intelligent. which not only satisfies the superiors. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t only satisfy the requirements for strict examination of abroad certification required by superiors, but also solves the problems caused by the lack of timely review of teachers and students.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Project] Campus intelligent auditing system based on Deep Learning and WeChat Applet</title>
      <link>/accomplishment/yangjin-pro-nationalutp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/accomplishment/yangjin-pro-nationalutp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Based on Natural Language Processing and WeChat Applet, this project designs a set of convenient proof of study and campus activity review system, which makes the process of issuing student certificates and campus activities approval standardized, institutionalized, procedural and intelligent. which not only satisfies the superiors. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t only satisfy the requirements for strict examination of abroad certification required by superiors, but also solves the problems caused by the lack of timely review of teachers and students.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Publication] Exploring Spatio-Temporal Representations by Integrating Attention-based Bidirectional-LSTM-RNNs and FCNs for Speech Emotion Recognition</title>
      <link>/accomplishment/zhaoyiqin-pub-exploringst/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/accomplishment/zhaoyiqin-pub-exploringst/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.isca-speech.org/archive/Interspeech_2018/pdfs/1477.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;PDF&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;abstract&#34;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Automatic emotion recognition from speech, which is an important and challenging task in the field of affective computing, heavily relies on the effectiveness of the speech features for classification. Previous approaches to emotion recognition have mostly focused on the extraction of carefully hand-crafted features. How to model spatio-temporal dynamics for speech emotion recognition effectively is still under active investigation. In this paper, we propose a method to tackle the problem of emotional relevant feature extraction from speech by leveraging Attention-based Bidirectional Long Short-Term Memory Recurrent Neural Networks with fully convolutional networks in order to automatically learn the best spatio-temporal representations of speech signals. The learned high-level features are then fed into a deep neural network (DNN) to predict the final emotion. The experimental results on the Chinese Natural Audio-Visual Emotion Database (CHEAVD) and the Interactive Emotional Dyadic Motion Capture (IEMOCAP) corpora show that our method provides more accurate predictions compared with other existing emotion recognition algorithms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;cite&#34;&gt;Cite&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;@inproceedings{Zhao2018,
  author={Ziping Zhao and Yu Zheng and Zixing Zhang and Haishuai Wang and Yiqin Zhao and Chao Li},
  title={Exploring Spatio-Temporal Representations by Integrating Attention-based Bidirectional-LSTM-RNNs and FCNs for Speech Emotion Recognition},
  year=2018,
  booktitle={Proc. Interspeech 2018},
  pages={272--276},
  doi={10.21437/Interspeech.2018-1477},
  url={http://dx.doi.org/10.21437/Interspeech.2018-1477}
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Award] National third award on 2017 China Collegiate Computing Contest (Top 6%)</title>
      <link>/accomplishment/zhaoyiqin-awd-cccc2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/accomplishment/zhaoyiqin-awd-cccc2017/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This contest is held by Zhejiang University and Apple, Inc to all students over the great China area. In this contest, we proposed an innovative iOS mobile App, Pece. Pece is foucsed on mental health and provide many professional psychology guide to help people to reduce pressure and stay in healthy mental state.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;video id=&#34;video&#34; controls=&#34;&#34; style=&#34;width: 100%&#34;&gt;
&lt;source id=&#34;mp4&#34; src=&#34;https://cdn.coden.hk/c422/assets/zhaoyiqin/pece/PC1MinVideo.mov&#34; type=&#34;video/mp4&#34;&gt;
&lt;/video&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other resources&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://cdn.coden.hk/c422/assets/zhaoyiqin/pece/PCKeynote.key&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Keynote&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://cdn.coden.hk/c422/assets/zhaoyiqin/pece/2017%E7%A7%BB%E5%8A%A8%E5%BA%94%E7%94%A8%E5%88%9B%E6%96%B0%E8%B5%9B-%E5%88%9D%E8%B5%9B.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Document&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Project] Depression Detection Software Based on Speech and Tune</title>
      <link>/accomplishment/zhaoyiqin-pro-nationalutp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/accomplishment/zhaoyiqin-pro-nationalutp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TODO: Add details&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Award] National third award on 2016 China Collegiate Computing Contest (Top 10%)</title>
      <link>/accomplishment/zhaoyiqin-awd-cccc2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/accomplishment/zhaoyiqin-awd-cccc2016/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This contest is held by Zhejiang University and Apple, Inc to all students over the great China area.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
