<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors on C422</title>
    <link>/authors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Authors on C422</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>C422 &amp;copy; {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/authors/jiaojinlong/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/authors/jiaojinlong/</guid>
      <description>I am an undergraduate software engineering student at Tianjin Normal University, Tianjin, China. I am a core member of iOS Club and I have attended Apple Summer Camp Nanjing of China, 2018. Additionaly, I am a key member of the Cognitive and Affective Computing Lab from Center for Affective Intelligence International Studies at my TJNU, advised by Prof. Ziping Zhao.
Currently participating in the project development of “support theory and innovation model of healthy pension cross-border service”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/authors/wangpenghao/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/authors/wangpenghao/</guid>
      <description>I am a sophomore major in software engineering at Tianjin Normal University, Tianjin, China. I am a core member of iOS Club. Besides, I am a key member of the Cognitive and Affective Computing Lab at my TJNU, advised by Prof. Ziping Zhao.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/authors/lisen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/authors/lisen/</guid>
      <description>Sen Li.
A 2017 undergraduate student in software engineering at Tianjin Normal University.
A member of the Cognitive and Affective Computing Lab at Tianjin Normal University,advised by Prof. Ziping Zhao.
Currently participating in the project development of &amp;ldquo;support theory and innovation model of healthy pension cross-border service&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/authors/zhaoyiqin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/authors/zhaoyiqin/</guid>
      <description>I am a senior undergaduate Software Engineeering student at Tianjin Normal University, Tianjin, China. I am also a key member of the Cognitive and Affective Computing Lab advised by Prof. Ziping Zhao at TJNU. I love both research and industrial, I had a wonderful internship experience at Baidu DuerOS department major in web development.
My research at TJNU is focused on applied machine learning and affective computing. If you are interested, checkout my selected projects and publications at below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/authors/yangjin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/authors/yangjin/</guid>
      <description>Now I am studying software engineering at Tianjin Normal University. I have a strong interest in computer programming languages ​​and machine learning models, and like to brainstorm and organize my own knowledge system.
Competition experience: As a project member, I participated in the tenth section of China University Student Service Outsourcing Innovation and Entrepreneurship Competition. As the project leader, I established Tianjin Normal University School-level Daiso Project.
Research direction: The main research direction at present is machine learning and computer networks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>We are C422 studio at Department of Computer and Information Engineering, Tianjin Normal University. Our community members mostly came from undergraduate students at our collage. Our activities are rooted in the combination of creativity development, academic research and more advanced technologies.
To accomplish this mission, we aim for technologies, design and high level research by a constructive, positive, innovative-driven attitude in all the work we undertake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>jinyang</title>
      <link>/authors/jinyang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/authors/jinyang/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>