<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>C422</title>
    <link>/authors/jiaojinlong/</link>
    <description>Recent content on C422</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>C422 &amp;copy; {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/authors/jiaojinlong/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Award] National third award on 2019 China Collegiate Computing Contest (Top 2.5%)</title>
      <link>/accomplishment/jiaojinlong-awd-cccc2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/accomplishment/jiaojinlong-awd-cccc2019/</guid>
      <description>This contest is held by Tsinghua University, Nankai University and Bytes Bounce Company, Inc to all students over the great China area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Keynote] Research share</title>
      <link>/post/keynote-20190525-jiaojinlong/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/keynote-20190525-jiaojinlong/</guid>
      <description>Weekly keynote, topic Research share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Project]  Hierachical Attention for Speech Emotion Recognition</title>
      <link>/accomplishment/jiaojinlong-pro-nationalutp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/accomplishment/jiaojinlong-pro-nationalutp/</guid>
      <description>Using hierarchical attention mechanisms at the level of sentences and words to improve the accuracy of speech emotion recognition. This project is supported by National Natural Science Foundation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Project] Research on Supporting Theory and Innovation Model of Cross-border Service for Healthy Elders</title>
      <link>/accomplishment/lisen-pro-pension/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/accomplishment/lisen-pro-pension/</guid>
      <description>In view of the problems existing in the credit information of China&amp;rsquo;s old-age care industry, in order to establish a sound old-age service credit information system and guarantee the quality of old-age service, the standard of pension service credit standard and the trust mechanism and reputation algorithm based on old-age service are formulated for development. The Health Support + “Integrated Support Platform provides theoretical support for credit assessment and provides a comprehensive solution for the credit problems in the aged care service. The project is supported by the National Key Basic Research Development Program (973 Program).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/authors/jiaojinlong/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/authors/jiaojinlong/</guid>
      <description>I am an undergraduate software engineering student at Tianjin Normal University, Tianjin, China. I am a core member of iOS Club and I have attended Apple Summer Camp Nanjing of China, 2018. Additionaly, I am a key member of the Cognitive and Affective Computing Lab from Center for Affective Intelligence International Studies at my TJNU, advised by Prof. Ziping Zhao.
Currently participating in the project development of “support theory and innovation model of healthy pension cross-border service”.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>