<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>C422</title>
    <link>/authors/lisen/</link>
    <description>Recent content on C422</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>C422 &amp;copy; {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/authors/lisen/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Publication] Design and Implementation of Credit Evaluation System for Healthy Aged Service</title>
      <link>/accomplishment/lisen-pub-pension/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/accomplishment/lisen-pub-pension/</guid>
      <description>Oral paper on 2019 IEEE SERVICES WORKSHOP ON HEALTHCARE SERVICES.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Project] Research on Supporting Theory and Innovation Model of Cross-border Service for Healthy Elders</title>
      <link>/accomplishment/lisen-pro-pension/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/accomplishment/lisen-pro-pension/</guid>
      <description>In view of the problems existing in the credit information of China&amp;rsquo;s old-age care industry, in order to establish a sound old-age service credit information system and guarantee the quality of old-age service, the standard of pension service credit standard and the trust mechanism and reputation algorithm based on old-age service are formulated for development. The Health Support + “Integrated Support Platform provides theoretical support for credit assessment and provides a comprehensive solution for the credit problems in the aged care service. The project is supported by the National Key Basic Research Development Program (973 Program).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Award] CADC 2018 China Aeromodelling Design Challenge · The First Prize</title>
      <link>/accomplishment/lisen-awd-cadc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/accomplishment/lisen-awd-cadc/</guid>
      <description>This contest is held at Nanjing,China , Inc to all students over the great China area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/authors/lisen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/authors/lisen/</guid>
      <description>Sen Li.
A 2017 undergraduate student in software engineering at Tianjin Normal University.
A member of the Cognitive and Affective Computing Lab at Tianjin Normal University,advised by Prof. Ziping Zhao.
Currently participating in the project development of &amp;ldquo;support theory and innovation model of healthy pension cross-border service&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>