<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Project on C422</title>
    <link>/tags/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Project on C422</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>C422 &amp;copy; {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Project]  Hierachical Attention for Speech Emotion Recognition</title>
      <link>/accomplishment/jiaojinlong-pro-nationalutp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/accomplishment/jiaojinlong-pro-nationalutp/</guid>
      <description>Using hierarchical attention mechanisms at the level of sentences and words to improve the accuracy of speech emotion recognition. This project is supported by National Natural Science Foundation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Project] Research on Supporting Theory and Innovation Model of Cross-border Service for Healthy Elders</title>
      <link>/accomplishment/lisen-pro-pension/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/accomplishment/lisen-pro-pension/</guid>
      <description>In view of the problems existing in the credit information of China&amp;rsquo;s old-age care industry, in order to establish a sound old-age service credit information system and guarantee the quality of old-age service, the standard of pension service credit standard and the trust mechanism and reputation algorithm based on old-age service are formulated for development. The Health Support + “Integrated Support Platform provides theoretical support for credit assessment and provides a comprehensive solution for the credit problems in the aged care service. The project is supported by the National Key Basic Research Development Program (973 Program).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Project] Campus intelligent auditing system based on Deep Learning and WeChat Applet</title>
      <link>/accomplishment/yangjin-pro-nationalutp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/accomplishment/yangjin-pro-nationalutp/</guid>
      <description>2018 Tianjin School level National Undergraduate Training Programs for Innovation and Entrepreneurship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Project] Depression Detection Software Based on Speech and Tune</title>
      <link>/accomplishment/zhaoyiqin-pro-nationalutp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/accomplishment/zhaoyiqin-pro-nationalutp/</guid>
      <description>2017 Tianjin Province level National Undergraduate Training Programs for Innovation and Entrepreneurship.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>